Preliminary Inventory to the W. Glenn Campbell Papers, 1945-1999
Hoover Institution Archives
W. Glenn Campbell Papers,
1945-1999
89009
Campbell, W. Glenn (Wesley Glenn), 1924-
96 manuscript boxes (40 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Agenda and minutes of meetings, conference proceedings, correspondence, memoranda, reports, studies, budgets, working papers, press releases, and printed matter, relating primarily to activities of the National Science Foundation in promoting scientific research and education in the United States; activities of the Japan-United States Friendship Commission in promoting academic and cultural ties between Japan and the United States; and administration of the University of California system
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1989.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
National Science Foundation (U.S.); Science--United States; Education--United States; Education; United States--Politics and government; United States--Foreign relations; Japan-United States Friendship Commission; United States--Relations--Japan; Japan--Relations--United States; Intellectual cooperation; University of California (System); Universities and colleges--United States; Japan
Container List
- NATIONAL SCIENCE FOUNDATION, 1971-1978
  - General (Box 1)
    - General
    - Membership
    - Organization
    - Rules and regulations
  - Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 2)
  - Meetings. Agenda, minutes, correspondence, memoranda, reports, and miscellany, primarily relating to the National Science Board (Box 3)
    - 1972 September. 150th meeting
    - 1972 October. 150th meeting (Box 4)
    - 1972 November. 151st meeting (Box 5)
    - 1973 January. 152nd meeting (Box 6)
    - 1973 February. 153rd meeting (Box 7)
    - 1973 March-April. 154th-155th meeting (Box 8)
    - 1973 May. 156th meeting (Box 9)
    - 1973 June. 157th meeting (Box 10)
    - 1973 September. 158th meeting (Box 11)
    - 1973 October-November. 159th-160th meeting (Box 12)
    - 1974 January-February. 161st-162nd meeting (Box 13)
    - 1974 March. 163rd meeting (Box 14)
    - Seminar on Scientific and Technical Manpower Projections, 1974 April
    - 1974 May. 164th meeting (Box 15)
    - 1974 June. 165th meeting (Box 16)
    - 1974 September. 166th meeting (Box 17)
    - 1974 October-November. 167th-168th meeting (Box 18)
    - 1975 January-February. 169th-170th meeting (Box 19)
    - 1975 March-April. 171st-172nd meeting (Box 20)
    - 1975 May-June. 173rd-174th meeting (Box 21)
    - 1975 September. 175th meeting (Box 22)
    - 1975 October-November. 176th-177th meeting (Box 23)
    - 1976 January. 178th meeting (Box 24)
    - 1976 February. 179th meeting (Box 25)
    - 1976 March. 180th meeting (Box 26)
    - 1976 May. 181st meeting (Box 27)
    - 1976 June. 182nd meeting (Box 28)
    - 1976 August. 183rd meeting (Box 29)
    - 1976 September. 184th meeting (Box 30)
    - 1976 October. 185th meeting (Box 31)
    - 1976 November. 186th meeting (Box 32)
    - 1977 February. 187th meeting (Box 33)
    - 1977 March. 188th meeting (Box 34)
    - 1977 April. 189th meeting (Box 35)
    - 1977 May-June. 190th-191st meeting (Box 36)
    - 1977 August. 192nd meeting (Box 37)
    - 1977 September. 193rd meeting (Box 38)
    - 1977 November. 194th meeting (Box 39)
    - 1978 January. 195th meeting (Box 40)
    - 1978 March. 196th meeting (Box 41)
    - 1978 April. 197th meeting (Box 42)
    - 1978 May. 198th meeting (Box 43)
  - Press releases, 1973-1798 (Box 44)
  - Printed material
    - General
    - General (Box 45)
    - NSF publications
      - General
      - General (Box 46)
      - Annual reports, 1971-1976
  - Subject file (Box 47)
    - General
      - Grants. Proposals, memoranda, and miscellany, 1972-1978
      - Speeches and writings by others, 1973-1977 (Box 48)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Board Organization (Box 49)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Action Review Boards
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Agenda
    - Ad Hoc Committee on N.S.B. Research Support
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Nominations for Board Officers
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the House Peer Review Report
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Social Sciences
    - Advisory Commitees - General (Box 50)
    - Advisory Committee on Planning and Institutional Affairs
    - Antarctica Program
    - Committee on Budget (Box 51)
    - Committee on Education and Curriculum Development
    - Committee on National Science Policy (Box 52)
    - Committee on Planning and Policy (Box 53)
      - General
      - General (Box 54)
      - Subcommittee on International Science Activities
      - Subcommittee on Manpower (Box 55)
      - Subcommittee on N.S.F. Support for Basic Research in Industry
      - Subcommittee on Policy Agenda
    - Committee on Programs
    - Committee on Role of N.S.F. in Basic Research (Box 56-57)
    - Man: A Course of Study (Box 58)
    - Planning and Environment Review Task Force
    - Research and Development Incentives Program (Box 59)
    - Research Applied to National Needs
    - Science Information Activities
    - Science for Citizens
    - Science and Society
    - Scientific Foreign Exchange Programs
    - Task Force "C"
- UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA REGENTS.
  Minutes and other material relating to meetings of the University of California Board of Regents, 1967-1969
  - 1967 January-September (Box 60)
  - 1967 October-1968 March (Box 61)
  - 1968 April-May (Box 62)
  - 1968 June-July (Box 63)
  - 1968 September (Box 64)
  - 1968 October (Box 65)
  - 1968 November (Box 66)
  - 1969 January (Box 67)
  - 1969 March (Box 68)
  - 1969 April (Box 69)
  - 1969 May (Box 70)
  - 1969 June (Box 71)
  - 1969 July (Box 72)
  - 1969 August (Box 73)
  - 1969 October (Box 74)
  - 1969 November (Box 75)
  - 1969 December (Box 76)
  - 1969 December (Box 77)
- JAPAN-UNITED STATES FRIENDSHIP COMMISSION, 1983-1989
  - 1983 (Box 77.)
    - Annual report
    - Key documents
    - East-West Center information
    - Material from Japan trip, 1983 April (Box 78)
    - Meeting, September 19
    - Meeting, September 19 (Box 79)
  - 1984
    - General
    - Meeting, April 8-9
    - Meeting, April 8-9 (Box 80)
    - Congressional hearing, March 16
    - Meeting, April 14
    - Bishirjian, Richard J.
    - Education Department grant
    - Program announcements
    - Presidential Commission on the Conduct of U.S.-Japan Relations. Includes report entitled Challenges and Opportunities in United States-Japan Relations
    - Commission visit to Japan, May 19-25 (Box 81)
    - CULCON XII, July 9-11
    - Meeting, September 19-20
    - Meeting, September 19-20 (Box 82)
    - Folder relating to upcoming visit to United States by Yasuhiro Nakasone
    - General correspondence, 1984-1985
  - 1985
    - Stewart, Roberta
    - Gangloff, Eric
    - Testimony for Congressional subcommittee, March
    - Programs
    - Sloan, Lindley S. (Box 83)
    - Trip to Japan, May
    - Meeting, April 14 (Box 84)
    - CULCON Steering Committee meeting, September 6
    - Trip material, April 1-3
    - Asia Foundation
    - Japan Society
    - Sloan, Lindley to grantees
    - Brochure
    - Ericson, Richard A., Jr.
    - Meeting, September 22-23 (Box 85)
  - 1985-1986. Annual report
  - 1986
    - Congressional testimony (Box 86)
    - CULCON XIII
    - Proposals
    - Japan-Funded U.S.-Based organizations
    - Fund raising
    - Newspaper clippings
    - Japan
    - Committee on Japanese Economic Studies
    - Budget for FY 1986
    - Brochures
    - Takeshita cabinet
    - Nakesone cabinet
    - New Advisory Group
    - Meeting, April 21-22
    - Meeting, September 21-23
  - 1987
    - Educational reform (Box 87)
    - Hall, Ivan P.
    - Japan/ROC
    - Taiwan/Japan
    - Congressional testimony
    - Membership
    - Abe, Shintaro
    - Schreiber, Joseph
    - National Conference of State Legislatures Japan Initiative
    - Meeting, April 26-27
    - Meeting, September 20-21
  - 1987-1988. Annual report (Box 88)
  - 1988
    - Correspondence
    - Congressional testimony
    - Regulations
    - "Japanese Studies in the 1980s: Surveys of Institutions and Individuals"
    - Ballots
    - CAUX Roundtable, August
    - Committees
    - Meeting, April 24-25
    - Meeting, September 19
    - CULCON XIV
  - 1989 (Box 89)
    - Correspondence
    - Memoranda
    - Congressional testimony, February
    - Reappointment
    - Myers, Ramon
    - Pamphlet
    - Meeting, April 26-27 (Box 90)
    - Meeting, April 26-27 (Box 91)
    - Final report by Campbell
- UNESCO MONITORING PANEL, 1983-1985
  - General (Box 92)
  - Budget, 1984-1985
  - Clippings
  - Correspondence
  - Meeting material
  - Meeting material (Box 93)
  - Reports
  - Reports (Box 94)
  - Speeches
- IRAN CONTRA INVESTIGATION.
  - Congressional report, chronology, and index, 1987 (Box 95)
- Incremental materials (Box 96)
  This addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archives know if you would like to see this material described.